[
  {
    "name": "PACK_1_NAME",
    "emoji": "ðŸ§ ",
    "questions": [
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_1",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_1",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_1_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_1_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_1_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_2",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_2",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_2_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_2_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_2_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_3",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_3",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_3_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_3_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_3_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_4",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_4",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_4_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_4_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_4_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_5",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_6",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_6",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_6_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_6_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_6_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_7",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_7",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_7_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_7_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_7_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_8",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_8",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_8_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_8_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_8_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_9",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_10",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_11",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_11",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_11_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_11_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_11_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_12",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_12",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_12_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_12_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_12_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_13",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_13",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_13_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_13_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_13_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_14",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_14",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_14_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_14_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_14_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_15",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_15",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_15_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_15_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_15_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_16",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_16",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_16_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_16_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_16_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_17",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_17",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_17_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_17_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_17_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_18",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_18",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_18_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_18_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_18_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_19",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_19",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_19_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_19_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_19_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_20",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_20",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_20_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_20_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_20_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_21",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_22",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_23",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_23",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_23_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_23_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_23_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_24",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_24",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_24_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_24_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_24_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_25",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_25",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_25_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_25_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_25_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_26",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_26",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_26_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_26_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_26_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_27",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_27",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_27_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_27_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_27_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_28",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_28",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_28_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_28_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_28_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_29",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_29",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_29_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_29_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_29_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_30",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_30",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_30_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_30_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_30_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_31",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_32",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_32",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_32_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_32_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_32_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_33",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_34",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_34",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_34_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_34_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_34_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_35",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_35",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_35_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_35_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_35_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_36",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_36",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_36_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_36_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_36_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_37",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_37",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_37_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_37_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_37_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_38",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_38",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_38_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_38_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_38_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_39",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_39",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_39_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_39_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_39_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_40",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_40",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_40_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_40_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_40_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_41",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_42",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_42",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_42_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_42_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_42_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_43",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_43",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_43_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_43_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_43_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_44",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_44",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_44_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_44_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_44_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_45",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_45",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_45_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_45_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_45_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_46",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_46",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_46_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_46_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_46_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_47",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_47",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_47_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_47_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_47_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_48",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_48",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_48_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_48_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_48_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_49",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_49",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_49_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_49_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_49_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_50",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_50",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_50_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_50_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_50_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_51",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_51",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_51_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_51_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_51_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_52",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_52",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_52_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_52_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_52_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_53",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_54",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_55",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_55",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_55_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_55_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_55_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_56",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_56",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_56_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_56_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_56_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_57",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_57",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_57_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_57_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_57_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_58",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_58",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_58_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_58_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_58_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_59",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_60",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_60",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_60_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_60_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_60_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_61",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_62",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_62",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_62_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_62_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_62_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_63",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_63",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_63_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_63_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_63_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_64",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_64",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_64_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_64_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_64_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_65",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_65",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_65_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_65_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_65_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_66",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_66",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_66_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_66_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_66_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_67",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_68",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_69",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_70",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_71",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_71",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_71_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_71_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_71_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_72",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_72",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_72_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_72_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_72_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_73",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_73",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_73_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_73_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_73_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_74",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_74",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_74_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_74_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_74_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_75",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_75",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_75_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_75_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_75_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_76",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_76",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_76_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_76_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_76_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_77",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_78",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_78",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_78_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_78_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_78_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_79",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_79",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_79_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_79_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_79_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_80",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_80",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_80_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_80_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_80_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_81",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_81",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_81_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_81_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_81_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_82",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_82",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_82_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_82_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_82_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_83",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_83",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_83_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_83_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_83_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_84",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_84",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_84_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_84_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_84_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_85",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_85",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_85_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_85_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_85_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_86",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_86",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_86_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_86_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_86_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_87",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_88",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_88",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_88_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_88_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_88_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_89",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_89",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_89_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_89_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_89_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_90",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_90",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_90_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_90_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_90_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_91",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_91",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_91_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_91_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_91_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_92",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_92",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_92_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_92_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_92_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_93",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_93",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_93_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_93_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_93_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_94",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_94",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_94_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_94_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_94_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_95",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_95",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_95_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_95_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_95_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_96",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_96",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_96_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_96_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_96_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_97",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_98",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_98",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_98_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_98_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_98_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_99",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_99",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_99_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_99_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_99_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_100",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_100",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_100_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_100_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_100_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_101",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_101",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_101_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_101_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_101_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_102",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_102",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_102_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_102_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_102_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_103",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_103",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_103_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_103_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_103_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_104",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_105",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_106",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_106",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_106_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_106_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_106_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_107",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_107",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_107_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_107_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_107_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_108",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_108",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_108_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_108_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_108_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_109",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_109",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_109_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_109_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_109_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_110",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_111",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_111",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_111_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_111_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_111_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_112",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_112",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_112_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_112_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_112_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_113",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_114",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_114",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_114_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_114_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_114_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_115",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_115",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_115_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_115_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_115_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_116",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_116",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_116_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_116_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_116_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_117",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_117",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_117_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_117_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_117_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_118",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_118",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_118_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_118_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_118_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_119",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_119",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_119_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_119_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_119_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_120",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_120",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_120_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_120_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_120_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_121",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_121",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_121_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_121_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_121_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_122",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_123",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_123",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_123_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_123_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_123_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_124",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_124",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_124_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_124_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_124_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_125",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_126",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_127",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_127",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_127_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_127_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_127_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_128",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_128",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_128_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_128_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_128_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_129",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_130",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_130",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_130_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_130_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_130_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_131",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_131",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_131_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_131_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_131_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_132",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_132",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_132_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_132_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_132_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_133",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_134",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_134",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_134_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_134_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_134_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_135",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_135",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_135_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_135_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_135_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_136",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_137",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_137",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_137_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_137_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_137_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_138",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_138",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_138_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_138_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_138_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_139",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_139",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_139_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_139_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_139_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_140",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_140",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_140_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_140_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_140_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_141",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_141",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_141_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_141_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_141_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_142",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_142",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_142_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_142_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_142_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_143",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_143",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_143_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_143_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_143_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_144",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_145",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_146",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_146",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_146_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_146_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_146_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_147",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_147",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_147_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_147_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_147_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_148",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_148",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_148_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_148_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_148_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_149",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_150",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_150",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_150_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_150_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_150_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_151",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_152",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_153",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_153",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_153_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_153_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_153_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_154",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_155",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_155",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_155_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_155_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_155_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_156",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_157",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_157",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_157_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_157_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_157_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_158",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_158",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_158_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_158_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_158_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_159",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_159",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_159_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_159_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_159_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_160",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_161",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_162",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_163",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_163",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_163_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_163_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_163_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_164",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_164",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_164_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_164_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_164_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_165",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_165",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_165_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_165_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_165_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_166",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_166",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_166_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_166_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_166_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_167",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_167",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_167_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_167_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_167_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_168",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_168",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_168_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_168_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_168_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_169",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_170",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_170",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_170_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_170_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_170_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_171",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_171",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_171_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_171_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_171_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_172",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_172",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_172_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_172_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_172_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_173",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_173",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_173_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_173_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_173_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_174",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_174",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_174_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_174_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_174_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_175",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_175",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_175_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_175_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_175_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_176",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_177",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_177",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_177_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_177_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_177_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_178",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_179",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_179",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_179_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_179_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_179_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_180",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_181",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_181",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_181_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_181_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_181_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_182",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_182",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_182_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_182_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_182_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_183",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_183",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_183_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_183_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_183_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_184",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_184",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_184_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_184_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_184_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_185",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_185",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_185_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_185_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_185_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_186",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_186",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_186_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_186_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_186_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_187",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_187",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_187_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_187_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_187_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_188",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_188",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_188_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_188_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_188_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_189",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_189",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_189_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_189_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_189_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_190",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_190",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_190_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_190_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_190_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_191",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_191",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_191_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_191_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_191_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_192",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_192",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_192_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_192_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_192_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_193",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_194",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_194",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_194_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_194_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_194_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_195",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_196",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_196",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_196_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_196_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_196_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_197",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_198",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_199",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_199",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_199_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_199_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_199_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_200",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_200",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_200_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_200_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_200_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_201",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_202",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_202",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_202_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_202_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_202_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_203",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_203",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_203_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_203_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_203_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_204",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_204",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_204_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_204_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_204_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_205",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_205",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_205_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_205_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_205_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_206",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_207",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_208",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_208",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_208_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_208_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_208_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_209",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_210",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_210",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_210_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_210_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_210_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_211",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_211",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_211_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_211_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_211_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_212",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_213",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_214",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_214",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_214_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_214_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_214_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_215",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_215",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_215_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_215_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_215_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_216",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_216",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_216_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_216_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_216_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_217",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_217",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_217_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_217_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_217_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_218",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_218",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_218_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_218_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_218_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_219",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_219",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_219_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_219_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_219_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_220",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_220",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_220_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_220_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_220_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_221",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_222",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_222",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_222_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_222_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_222_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_223",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_224",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_224",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_224_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_224_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_224_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_225",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_225",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_225_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_225_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_225_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_226",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_226",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_226_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_226_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_226_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_227",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_227",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_227_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_227_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_227_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_228",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_228",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_228_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_228_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_228_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_229",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_229",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_229_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_229_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_229_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_230",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_230",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_230_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_230_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_230_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_231",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_231",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_231_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_231_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_231_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_232",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_232",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_232_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_232_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_232_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_233",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_233",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_233_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_233_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_233_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_234",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_234",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_234_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_234_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_234_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_235",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_235",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_235_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_235_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_235_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_236",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_236",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_236_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_236_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_236_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_237",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_237",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_237_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_237_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_237_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_238",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_239",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_240",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_240",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_240_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_240_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_240_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_241",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_241",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_241_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_241_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_241_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_242",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_242",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_242_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_242_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_242_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_243",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_243",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_243_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_243_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_243_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_244",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_244",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_244_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_244_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_244_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_245",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_245",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_245_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_245_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_245_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_246",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_246",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_246_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_246_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_246_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_247",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_247",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_247_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_247_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_247_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_248",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_248",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_248_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_248_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_248_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_249",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_249",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_249_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_249_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_249_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_250",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_250",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_250_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_250_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_250_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_251",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_251",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_251_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_251_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_251_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_252",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_252",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_252_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_252_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_252_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_253",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_253",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_253_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_253_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_253_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_254",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_255",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_255",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_255_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_255_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_255_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_256",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_256",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_256_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_256_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_256_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_257",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_257",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_257_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_257_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_257_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_258",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_258",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_258_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_258_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_258_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_259",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_259",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_259_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_259_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_259_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_260",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_261",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_261",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_261_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_261_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_261_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_262",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_262",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_262_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_262_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_262_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_263",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_264",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_264",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_264_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_264_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_264_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_265",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_266",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_266",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_266_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_266_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_266_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_267",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_267",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_267_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_267_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_267_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_268",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_268",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_268_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_268_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_268_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_269",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_269",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_269_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_269_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_269_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_270",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_270",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_270_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_270_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_270_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_271",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_271",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_271_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_271_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_271_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_272",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_272",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_272_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_272_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_272_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_273",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_273",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_273_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_273_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_273_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_274",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_274",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_274_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_274_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_274_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_275",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_276",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_276",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_276_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_276_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_276_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_277",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_277",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_277_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_277_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_277_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_278",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_278",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_278_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_278_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_278_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_279",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_279",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_279_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_279_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_279_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_280",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_280",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_280_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_280_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_280_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_281",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_281",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_281_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_281_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_281_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_282",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_282",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_282_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_282_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_282_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_283",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_283",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_283_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_283_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_283_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_284",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_284",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_284_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_284_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_284_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_285",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_285",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_285_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_285_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_285_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_286",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_287",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_287",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_287_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_287_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_287_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_288",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_288",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_288_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_288_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_288_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_289",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_289",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_289_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_289_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_289_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_290",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_290",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_290_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_290_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_290_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_291",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_291",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_291_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_291_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_291_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_292",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_292",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_292_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_292_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_292_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_293",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_293",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_293_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_293_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_293_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_294",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_294",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_294_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_294_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_294_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_295",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_296",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_296",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_296_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_296_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_296_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_297",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_297",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_297_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_297_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_297_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_298",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_298",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_298_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_298_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_298_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_299",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_299",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_299_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_299_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_299_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_1_QUESTION_300",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_1_CORRECT_ANSWER_300",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_300_1",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_300_2",
          "PACK_1_INCORRECT_ANSWER_300_3"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "PACK_2_NAME",
    "emoji": "ðŸ‘º",
    "questions": [
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_1",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_1",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_1_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_1_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_1_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_2",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_3",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_3",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_3_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_3_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_3_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_4",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_5",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_5",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_5_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_5_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_5_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_6",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_6",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_6_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_6_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_6_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_7",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_7",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_7_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_7_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_7_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_8",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_8",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_8_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_8_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_8_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_9",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_9",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_9_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_9_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_9_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_10",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_10",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_10_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_10_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_10_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_11",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_11",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_11_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_11_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_11_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_12",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_12",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_12_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_12_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_12_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_13",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_14",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_14",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_14_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_14_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_14_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_15",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_15",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_15_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_15_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_15_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_16",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_16",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_16_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_16_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_16_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_17",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_17",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_17_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_17_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_17_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_18",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_18",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_18_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_18_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_18_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_19",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_20",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_20",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_20_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_20_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_20_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_21",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_21",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_21_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_21_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_21_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_22",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_22",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_22_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_22_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_22_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_23",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_24",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_24",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_24_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_24_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_24_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_25",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_25",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_25_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_25_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_25_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_26",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_26",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_26_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_26_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_26_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_27",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_27",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_27_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_27_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_27_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_28",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_28",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_28_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_28_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_28_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_29",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_29",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_29_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_29_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_29_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_30",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_30",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_30_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_30_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_30_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_31",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_32",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_32",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_32_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_32_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_32_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_33",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_33",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_33_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_33_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_33_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_34",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_34",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_34_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_34_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_34_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_35",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_36",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_36",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_36_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_36_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_36_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_37",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_38",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_38",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_38_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_38_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_38_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_39",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_40",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_40",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_40_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_40_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_40_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_41",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_41",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_41_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_41_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_41_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_42",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_42",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_42_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_42_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_42_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_43",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_44",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_44",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_44_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_44_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_44_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_45",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_45",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_45_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_45_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_45_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_46",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_46",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_46_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_46_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_46_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_47",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_47",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_47_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_47_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_47_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_48",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_48",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_48_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_48_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_48_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_49",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_49",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_49_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_49_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_49_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_50",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_50",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_50_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_50_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_50_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_51",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_51",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_51_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_51_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_51_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_52",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_52",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_52_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_52_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_52_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_53",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_54",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_54",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_54_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_54_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_54_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_55",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_55",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_55_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_55_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_55_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_56",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_56",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_56_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_56_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_56_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_57",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_57",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_57_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_57_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_57_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_58",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_58",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_58_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_58_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_58_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_59",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_59",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_59_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_59_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_59_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_60",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_60",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_60_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_60_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_60_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_61",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_61",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_61_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_61_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_61_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_62",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_63",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_64",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_64",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_64_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_64_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_64_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_65",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_65",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_65_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_65_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_65_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_66",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_66",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_66_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_66_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_66_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_67",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_67",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_67_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_67_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_67_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_68",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_68",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_68_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_68_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_68_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_69",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_70",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_70",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_70_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_70_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_70_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_71",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_71",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_71_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_71_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_71_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_72",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_72",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_72_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_72_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_72_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_73",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_73",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_73_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_73_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_73_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_74",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_74",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_74_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_74_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_74_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_75",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_75",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_75_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_75_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_75_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_76",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_76",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_76_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_76_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_76_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_77",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_77",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_77_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_77_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_77_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_78",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_78",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_78_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_78_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_78_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_79",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_79",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_79_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_79_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_79_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_80",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_80",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_80_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_80_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_80_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_81",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_81",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_81_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_81_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_81_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_82",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_82",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_82_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_82_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_82_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_83",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_83",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_83_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_83_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_83_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_84",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_84",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_84_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_84_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_84_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_85",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_85",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_85_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_85_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_85_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_86",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_86",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_86_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_86_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_86_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_87",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_87",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_87_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_87_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_87_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_88",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_88",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_88_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_88_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_88_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_89",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_89",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_89_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_89_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_89_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_90",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_90",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_90_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_90_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_90_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_91",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_91",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_91_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_91_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_91_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_92",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_92",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_92_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_92_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_92_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_93",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_94",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_95",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_95",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_95_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_95_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_95_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_96",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_96",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_96_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_96_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_96_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_97",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_97",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_97_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_97_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_97_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_98",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_98",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_98_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_98_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_98_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_99",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_99",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_99_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_99_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_99_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_100",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_100",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_100_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_100_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_100_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_101",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_101",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_101_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_101_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_101_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_102",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_102",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_102_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_102_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_102_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_103",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_103",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_103_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_103_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_103_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_104",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_104",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_104_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_104_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_104_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_105",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_105",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_105_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_105_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_105_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_106",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_106",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_106_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_106_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_106_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_107",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_107",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_107_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_107_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_107_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_108",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_108",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_108_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_108_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_108_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_109",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_109",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_109_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_109_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_109_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_110",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_110",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_110_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_110_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_110_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_111",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_111",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_111_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_111_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_111_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_112",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_112",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_112_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_112_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_112_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_113",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_113",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_113_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_113_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_113_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_114",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_114",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_114_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_114_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_114_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_115",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_116",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_117",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_117",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_117_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_117_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_117_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_118",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_118",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_118_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_118_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_118_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_119",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_119",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_119_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_119_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_119_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_120",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_120",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_120_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_120_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_120_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_121",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_121",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_121_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_121_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_121_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_122",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_122",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_122_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_122_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_122_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_123",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_123",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_123_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_123_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_123_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_124",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_124",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_124_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_124_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_124_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_125",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_125",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_125_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_125_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_125_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_126",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_126",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_126_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_126_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_126_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_127",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_127",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_127_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_127_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_127_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_128",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_128",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_128_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_128_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_128_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_129",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_129",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_129_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_129_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_129_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_130",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_130",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_130_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_130_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_130_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_131",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_131",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_131_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_131_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_131_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_132",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_132",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_132_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_132_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_132_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_133",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_133",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_133_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_133_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_133_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_134",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_134",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_134_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_134_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_134_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_135",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_135",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_135_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_135_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_135_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_136",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_136",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_136_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_136_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_136_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_137",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_137",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_137_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_137_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_137_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_138",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_138",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_138_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_138_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_138_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_139",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_140",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_140",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_140_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_140_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_140_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_141",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_142",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_142",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_142_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_142_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_142_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_143",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_143",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_143_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_143_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_143_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_144",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_144",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_144_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_144_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_144_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_145",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_145",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_145_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_145_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_145_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_146",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_146",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_146_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_146_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_146_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_147",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_147",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_147_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_147_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_147_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_148",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_148",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_148_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_148_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_148_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_149",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_149",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_149_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_149_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_149_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_150",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_150",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_150_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_150_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_150_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_151",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_151",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_151_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_151_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_151_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_152",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_152",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_152_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_152_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_152_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_153",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_153",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_153_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_153_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_153_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_154",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_154",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_154_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_154_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_154_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_155",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_155",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_155_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_155_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_155_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_156",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_156",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_156_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_156_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_156_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_157",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_157",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_157_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_157_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_157_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_158",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_158",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_158_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_158_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_158_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_159",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_159",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_159_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_159_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_159_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_160",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_160",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_160_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_160_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_160_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_161",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_161",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_161_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_161_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_161_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_162",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_162",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_162_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_162_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_162_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_163",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_163",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_163_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_163_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_163_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_164",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_165",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_165",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_165_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_165_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_165_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_166",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_166",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_166_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_166_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_166_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_167",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_168",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_169",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_169",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_169_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_169_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_169_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_170",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_170",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_170_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_170_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_170_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_171",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_171",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_171_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_171_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_171_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_172",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_172",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_172_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_172_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_172_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_173",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_173",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_173_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_173_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_173_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_174",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_174",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_174_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_174_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_174_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_175",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_176",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_176",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_176_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_176_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_176_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_177",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_177",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_177_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_177_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_177_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_178",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_178",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_178_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_178_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_178_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_179",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_2_CORRECT_ANSWER_179",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_179_1",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_179_2",
          "PACK_2_INCORRECT_ANSWER_179_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_2_QUESTION_180",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "PACK_3_NAME",
    "emoji": "ðŸŽµ",
    "questions": [
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_1",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_1",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_1_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_1_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_1_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_2",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_2",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_2_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_2_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_2_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_3",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_3",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_3_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_3_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_3_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_4",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_5",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_5",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_5_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_5_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_5_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_6",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_6",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_6_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_6_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_6_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_7",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_7",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_7_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_7_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_7_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_8",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_8",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_8_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_8_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_8_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_9",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_9",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_9_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_9_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_9_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_10",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_10",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_10_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_10_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_10_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_11",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_11",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_11_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_11_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_11_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_12",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_12",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_12_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_12_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_12_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_13",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_13",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_13_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_13_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_13_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_14",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_14",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_14_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_14_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_14_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_15",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_15",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_15_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_15_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_15_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_16",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_17",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_17",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_17_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_17_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_17_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_18",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_18",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_18_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_18_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_18_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_19",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_19",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_19_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_19_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_19_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_20",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_20",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_20_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_20_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_20_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_21",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_21",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_21_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_21_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_21_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_22",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_22",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_22_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_22_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_22_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_23",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_23",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_23_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_23_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_23_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_24",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_24",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_24_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_24_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_24_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_25",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_26",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_26",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_26_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_26_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_26_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_27",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_27",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_27_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_27_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_27_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_28",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_28",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_28_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_28_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_28_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_29",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_30",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_30",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_30_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_30_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_30_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_31",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_31",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_31_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_31_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_31_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_32",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_32",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_32_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_32_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_32_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_33",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_33",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_33_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_33_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_33_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_34",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_34",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_34_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_34_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_34_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_35",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_35",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_35_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_35_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_35_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_36",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_36",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_36_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_36_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_36_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_37",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_37",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_37_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_37_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_37_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_38",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_38",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_38_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_38_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_38_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_39",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_40",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_40",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_40_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_40_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_40_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_41",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_42",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_42",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_42_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_42_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_42_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_43",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_43",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_43_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_43_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_43_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_44",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_44",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_44_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_44_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_44_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_45",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_45",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_45_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_45_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_45_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_46",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_46",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_46_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_46_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_46_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_47",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_47",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_47_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_47_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_47_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_48",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_48",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_48_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_48_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_48_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_49",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_49",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_49_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_49_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_49_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_50",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_50",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_50_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_50_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_50_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_51",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_51",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_51_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_51_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_51_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_52",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_52",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_52_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_52_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_52_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_53",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_53",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_53_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_53_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_53_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_54",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_54",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_54_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_54_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_54_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_55",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_55",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_55_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_55_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_55_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_56",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_57",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_57",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_57_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_57_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_57_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_58",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_58",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_58_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_58_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_58_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_59",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_59",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_59_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_59_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_59_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_60",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_60",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_60_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_60_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_60_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_61",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_61",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_61_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_61_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_61_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_62",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_62",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_62_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_62_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_62_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_63",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_63",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_63_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_63_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_63_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_64",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_64",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_64_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_64_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_64_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_65",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_65",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_65_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_65_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_65_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_66",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_66",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_66_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_66_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_66_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_67",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_67",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_67_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_67_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_67_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_68",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_68",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_68_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_68_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_68_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_69",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_70",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_70",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_70_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_70_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_70_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_71",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_71",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_71_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_71_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_71_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_72",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_72",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_72_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_72_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_72_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_73",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_73",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_73_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_73_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_73_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_74",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_74",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_74_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_74_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_74_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_75",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_75",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_75_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_75_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_75_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_76",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_76",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_76_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_76_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_76_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_77",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_77",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_77_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_77_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_77_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_78",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_79",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_79",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_79_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_79_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_79_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_80",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_80",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_80_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_80_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_80_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_81",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_81",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_81_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_81_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_81_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_82",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_83",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_83",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_83_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_83_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_83_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_84",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_84",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_84_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_84_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_84_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_85",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_85",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_85_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_85_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_85_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_86",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_86",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_86_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_86_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_86_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_87",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_87",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_87_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_87_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_87_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_88",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_88",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_88_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_88_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_88_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_89",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_89",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_89_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_89_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_89_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_90",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_90",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_90_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_90_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_90_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_91",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_91",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_91_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_91_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_91_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_92",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_92",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_92_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_92_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_92_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_93",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_93",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_93_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_93_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_93_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_94",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_94",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_94_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_94_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_94_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_95",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_95",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_95_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_95_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_95_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_96",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_96",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_96_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_96_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_96_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_97",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_97",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_97_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_97_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_97_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_98",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_99",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_99",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_99_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_99_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_99_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_100",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_100",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_100_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_100_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_100_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_101",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_101",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_101_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_101_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_101_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_102",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_102",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_102_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_102_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_102_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_103",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_103",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_103_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_103_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_103_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_104",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_104",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_104_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_104_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_104_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_105",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_105",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_105_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_105_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_105_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_106",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_106",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_106_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_106_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_106_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_107",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_107",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_107_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_107_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_107_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_108",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_108",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_108_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_108_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_108_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_109",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_109",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_109_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_109_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_109_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_110",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_110",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_110_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_110_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_110_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_111",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_111",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_111_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_111_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_111_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_112",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_112",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_112_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_112_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_112_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_113",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_114",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_114",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_114_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_114_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_114_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_115",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_115",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_115_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_115_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_115_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_116",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_116",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_116_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_116_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_116_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_117",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_117",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_117_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_117_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_117_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_118",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_119",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_119",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_119_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_119_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_119_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_120",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_120",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_120_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_120_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_120_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_121",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_121",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_121_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_121_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_121_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_122",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_122",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_122_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_122_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_122_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_123",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_124",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_124",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_124_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_124_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_124_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_125",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_126",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_126",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_126_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_126_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_126_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_127",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_127",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_127_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_127_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_127_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_128",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_128",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_128_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_128_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_128_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_129",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_129",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_129_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_129_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_129_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_130",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_130",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_130_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_130_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_130_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_131",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_131",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_131_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_131_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_131_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_132",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_132",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_132_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_132_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_132_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_133",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_133",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_133_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_133_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_133_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_134",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_134",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_134_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_134_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_134_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_135",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_135",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_135_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_135_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_135_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_136",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_136",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_136_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_136_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_136_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_137",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_137",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_137_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_137_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_137_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_138",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_138",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_138_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_138_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_138_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_139",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_139",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_139_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_139_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_139_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_140",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_140",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_140_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_140_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_140_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_141",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_142",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_142",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_142_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_142_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_142_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_143",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_143",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_143_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_143_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_143_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_144",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_144",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_144_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_144_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_144_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_145",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_145",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_145_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_145_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_145_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_146",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_146",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_146_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_146_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_146_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_147",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_147",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_147_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_147_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_147_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_148",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_148",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_148_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_148_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_148_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_149",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_149",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_149_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_149_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_149_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_150",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_150",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_150_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_150_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_150_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_151",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_151",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_151_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_151_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_151_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_152",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_152",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_152_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_152_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_152_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_153",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_153",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_153_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_153_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_153_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_154",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_154",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_154_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_154_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_154_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_155",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_155",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_155_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_155_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_155_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_156",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_156",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_156_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_156_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_156_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_157",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_158",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_158",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_158_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_158_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_158_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_159",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_159",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_159_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_159_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_159_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_160",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_160",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_160_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_160_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_160_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_161",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_161",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_161_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_161_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_161_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_162",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_162",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_162_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_162_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_162_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_163",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_163",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_163_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_163_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_163_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_164",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_164",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_164_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_164_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_164_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_165",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_165",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_165_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_165_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_165_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_166",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_166",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_166_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_166_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_166_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_167",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_167",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_167_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_167_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_167_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_168",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_168",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_168_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_168_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_168_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_169",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_169",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_169_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_169_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_169_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_170",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_170",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_170_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_170_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_170_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_171",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_171",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_171_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_171_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_171_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_172",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_172",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_172_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_172_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_172_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_173",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_173",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_173_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_173_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_173_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_174",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_174",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_174_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_174_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_174_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_175",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_175",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_175_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_175_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_175_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_176",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_177",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_177",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_177_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_177_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_177_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_178",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_178",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_178_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_178_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_178_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_179",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_179",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_179_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_179_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_179_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_180",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_180",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_180_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_180_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_180_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_181",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_181",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_181_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_181_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_181_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_182",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_182",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_182_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_182_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_182_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_183",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_183",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_183_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_183_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_183_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_184",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_184",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_184_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_184_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_184_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_185",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_185",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_185_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_185_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_185_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_186",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_186",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_186_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_186_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_186_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_187",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_187",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_187_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_187_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_187_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_188",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_188",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_188_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_188_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_188_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_189",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_190",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_191",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_191",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_191_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_191_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_191_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_192",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_192",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_192_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_192_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_192_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_193",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_193",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_193_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_193_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_193_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_194",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_194",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_194_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_194_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_194_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_195",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_195",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_195_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_195_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_195_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_196",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_196",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_196_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_196_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_196_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_197",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_197",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_197_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_197_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_197_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_198",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_198",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_198_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_198_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_198_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_199",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_199",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_199_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_199_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_199_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_200",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_200",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_200_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_200_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_200_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_201",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_201",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_201_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_201_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_201_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_202",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_203",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_204",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_204",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_204_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_204_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_204_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_205",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_205",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_205_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_205_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_205_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_206",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_206",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_206_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_206_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_206_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_207",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_207",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_207_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_207_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_207_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_208",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_208",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_208_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_208_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_208_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_209",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_209",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_209_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_209_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_209_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_210",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_210",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_210_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_210_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_210_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_211",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_211",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_211_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_211_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_211_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_212",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_212",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_212_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_212_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_212_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_213",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_214",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_214",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_214_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_214_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_214_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_215",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_215",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_215_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_215_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_215_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_216",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_216",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_216_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_216_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_216_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_217",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_217",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_217_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_217_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_217_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_218",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_218",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_218_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_218_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_218_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_219",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_220",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_220",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_220_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_220_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_220_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_221",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_221",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_221_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_221_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_221_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_222",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_222",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_222_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_222_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_222_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_223",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_224",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_224",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_224_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_224_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_224_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_225",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_225",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_225_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_225_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_225_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_226",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_226",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_226_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_226_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_226_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_227",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_228",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_228",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_228_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_228_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_228_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_229",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_229",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_229_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_229_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_229_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_230",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_230",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_230_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_230_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_230_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_231",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_232",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_232",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_232_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_232_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_232_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_233",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_233",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_233_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_233_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_233_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_234",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_234",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_234_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_234_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_234_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_235",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_236",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_236",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_236_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_236_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_236_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_237",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_237",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_237_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_237_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_237_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_238",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_238",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_238_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_238_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_238_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_239",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_239",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_239_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_239_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_239_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_240",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_240",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_240_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_240_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_240_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_241",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_241",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_241_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_241_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_241_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_242",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_243",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_243",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_243_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_243_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_243_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_244",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_244",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_244_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_244_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_244_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_245",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_245",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_245_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_245_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_245_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_246",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_246",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_246_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_246_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_246_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_247",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_247",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_247_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_247_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_247_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_248",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_248",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_248_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_248_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_248_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_249",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_249",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_249_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_249_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_249_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_250",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_250",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_250_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_250_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_250_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_251",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_251",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_251_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_251_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_251_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_252",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_252",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_252_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_252_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_252_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_253",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_253",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_253_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_253_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_253_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_254",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_254",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_254_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_254_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_254_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_255",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_256",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_256",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_256_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_256_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_256_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_257",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_257",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_257_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_257_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_257_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_258",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_258",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_258_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_258_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_258_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_259",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_260",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_260",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_260_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_260_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_260_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_261",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_261",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_261_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_261_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_261_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_262",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_263",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_263",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_263_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_263_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_263_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_264",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_264",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_264_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_264_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_264_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_265",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_265",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_265_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_265_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_265_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_266",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_266",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_266_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_266_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_266_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_267",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_267",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_267_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_267_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_267_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_268",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_268",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_268_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_268_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_268_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_269",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_269",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_269_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_269_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_269_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_270",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_270",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_270_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_270_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_270_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_271",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_271",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_271_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_271_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_271_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_272",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_272",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_272_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_272_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_272_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_273",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_273",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_273_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_273_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_273_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_274",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_275",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_275",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_275_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_275_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_275_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_276",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_276",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_276_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_276_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_276_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_277",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_277",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_277_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_277_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_277_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_278",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_279",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_279",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_279_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_279_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_279_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_280",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_280",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_280_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_280_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_280_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_281",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_281",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_281_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_281_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_281_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_282",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_282",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_282_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_282_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_282_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_283",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_283",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_283_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_283_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_283_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_284",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_284",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_284_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_284_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_284_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_285",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_285",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_285_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_285_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_285_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_286",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_286",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_286_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_286_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_286_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_287",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_287",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_287_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_287_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_287_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_288",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_288",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_288_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_288_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_288_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_289",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_289",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_289_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_289_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_289_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_290",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_290",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_290_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_290_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_290_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_291",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_291",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_291_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_291_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_291_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_292",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_292",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_292_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_292_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_292_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_293",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_293",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_293_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_293_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_293_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_294",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_294",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_294_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_294_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_294_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_295",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_295",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_295_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_295_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_295_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_296",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_296",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_296_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_296_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_296_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_297",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_297",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_297_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_297_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_297_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_298",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_298",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_298_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_298_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_298_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_299",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_299",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_299_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_299_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_299_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_3_QUESTION_300",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_3_CORRECT_ANSWER_300",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_300_1",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_300_2",
          "PACK_3_INCORRECT_ANSWER_300_3"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "PACK_4_NAME",
    "emoji": "ðŸ’»",
    "questions": [
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_1",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_2",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_2",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_2_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_2_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_2_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_3",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_4",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_4",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_4_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_4_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_4_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_5",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_5",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_5_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_5_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_5_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_6",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_7",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_7",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_7_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_7_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_7_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_8",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_8",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_8_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_8_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_8_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_9",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_9",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_9_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_9_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_9_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_10",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_10",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_10_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_10_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_10_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_11",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_11",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_11_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_11_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_11_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_12",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_12",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_12_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_12_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_12_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_13",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_13",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_13_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_13_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_13_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_14",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_14",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_14_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_14_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_14_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_15",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_16",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_16",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_16_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_16_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_16_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_17",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_17",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_17_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_17_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_17_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_18",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_18",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_18_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_18_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_18_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_19",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_20",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_21",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_21",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_21_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_21_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_21_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_22",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_22",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_22_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_22_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_22_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_23",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_24",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_25",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_26",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_26",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_26_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_26_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_26_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_27",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_28",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_28",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_28_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_28_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_28_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_29",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_30",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_30",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_30_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_30_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_30_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_31",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_31",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_31_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_31_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_31_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_32",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_32",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_32_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_32_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_32_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_33",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_33",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_33_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_33_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_33_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_34",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_34",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_34_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_34_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_34_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_35",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_36",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_36",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_36_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_36_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_36_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_37",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_37",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_37_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_37_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_37_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_38",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_38",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_38_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_38_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_38_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_39",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_39",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_39_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_39_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_39_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_40",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_40",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_40_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_40_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_40_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_41",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_41",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_41_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_41_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_41_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_42",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_43",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_43",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_43_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_43_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_43_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_44",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_44",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_44_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_44_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_44_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_45",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_45",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_45_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_45_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_45_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_46",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_46",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_46_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_46_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_46_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_47",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_47",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_47_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_47_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_47_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_48",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_48",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_48_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_48_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_48_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_49",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_49",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_49_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_49_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_49_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_50",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_50",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_50_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_50_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_50_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_51",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_51",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_51_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_51_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_51_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_52",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_52",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_52_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_52_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_52_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_53",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_53",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_53_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_53_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_53_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_54",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_54",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_54_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_54_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_54_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_55",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_55",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_55_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_55_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_55_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_56",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_56",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_56_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_56_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_56_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_57",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_58",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_59",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_59",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_59_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_59_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_59_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_60",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_60",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_60_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_60_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_60_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_61",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_61",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_61_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_61_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_61_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_62",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_62",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_62_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_62_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_62_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_63",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_63",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_63_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_63_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_63_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_64",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_64",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_64_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_64_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_64_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_65",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_66",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_66",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_66_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_66_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_66_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_67",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_68",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_68",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_68_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_68_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_68_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_69",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_70",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_70",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_70_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_70_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_70_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_71",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_71",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_71_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_71_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_71_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_72",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_72",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_72_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_72_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_72_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_73",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_73",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_73_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_73_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_73_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_74",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_74",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_74_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_74_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_74_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_75",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_75",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_75_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_75_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_75_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_76",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_76",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_76_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_76_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_76_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_77",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_77",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_77_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_77_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_77_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_78",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_78",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_78_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_78_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_78_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_79",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_79",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_79_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_79_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_79_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_80",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_80",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_80_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_80_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_80_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_81",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_81",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_81_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_81_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_81_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_82",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_82",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_82_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_82_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_82_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_83",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_83",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_83_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_83_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_83_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_84",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_84",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_84_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_84_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_84_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_85",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_86",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_86",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_86_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_86_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_86_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_87",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_87",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_87_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_87_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_87_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_88",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_88",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_88_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_88_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_88_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_89",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_89",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_89_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_89_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_89_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_90",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_91",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_91",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_91_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_91_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_91_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_92",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_92",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_92_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_92_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_92_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_93",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_93",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_93_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_93_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_93_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_94",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_94",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_94_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_94_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_94_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_95",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_96",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_97",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_97",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_97_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_97_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_97_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_98",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_99",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_100",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_100",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_100_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_100_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_100_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_101",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_101",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_101_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_101_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_101_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_102",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_103",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_103",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_103_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_103_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_103_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_104",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_104",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_104_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_104_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_104_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_105",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_105",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_105_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_105_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_105_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_106",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_106",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_106_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_106_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_106_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_107",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_107",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_107_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_107_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_107_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_108",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_108",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_108_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_108_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_108_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_109",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_109",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_109_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_109_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_109_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_110",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_110",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_110_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_110_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_110_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_111",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_111",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_111_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_111_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_111_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_112",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_112",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_112_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_112_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_112_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_113",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_114",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_114",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_114_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_114_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_114_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_115",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_115",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_115_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_115_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_115_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_116",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_116",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_116_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_116_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_116_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_117",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_117",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_117_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_117_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_117_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_118",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_118",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_118_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_118_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_118_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_119",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_119",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_119_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_119_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_119_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_120",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_121",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_121",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_121_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_121_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_121_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_122",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_122",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_122_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_122_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_122_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_123",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_123",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_123_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_123_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_123_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_124",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_124",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_124_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_124_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_124_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_125",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_125",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_125_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_125_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_125_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_126",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_126",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_126_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_126_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_126_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_127",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_128",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_128",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_128_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_128_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_128_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_129",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_130",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_130",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_130_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_130_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_130_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_131",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_132",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_132",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_132_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_132_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_132_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_133",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_133",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_133_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_133_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_133_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_134",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_134",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_134_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_134_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_134_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_135",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_135",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_135_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_135_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_135_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_136",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_136",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_136_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_136_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_136_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_137",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_137",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_137_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_137_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_137_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_138",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_139",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_139",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_139_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_139_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_139_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_140",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_140",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_140_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_140_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_140_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_141",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_141",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_141_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_141_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_141_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_142",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_142",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_142_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_142_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_142_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_143",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_143",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_143_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_143_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_143_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_144",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_144",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_144_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_144_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_144_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_145",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_146",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_146",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_146_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_146_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_146_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_147",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_148",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_148",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_148_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_148_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_148_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_149",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_149",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_149_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_149_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_149_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_4_QUESTION_150",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_4_CORRECT_ANSWER_150",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_150_1",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_150_2",
          "PACK_4_INCORRECT_ANSWER_150_3"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "PACK_5_NAME",
    "emoji": "ðŸƒ",
    "questions": [
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_1",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_2",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_3",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_4",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_4",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_4_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_4_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_4_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_5",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_5",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_5_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_5_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_5_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_6",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_6",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_6_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_6_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_6_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_7",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_8",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_8",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_8_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_8_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_8_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_9",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_9",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_9_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_9_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_9_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_10",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_10",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_10_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_10_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_10_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_11",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_12",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_12",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_12_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_12_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_12_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_13",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_13",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_13_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_13_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_13_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_14",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_14",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_14_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_14_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_14_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_15",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_16",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_17",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_17",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_17_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_17_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_17_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_18",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_18",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_18_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_18_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_18_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_19",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_19",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_19_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_19_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_19_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_20",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_20",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_20_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_20_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_20_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_21",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_21",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_21_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_21_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_21_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_22",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_22",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_22_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_22_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_22_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_23",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_23",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_23_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_23_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_23_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_24",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_25",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_25",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_25_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_25_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_25_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_26",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_26",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_26_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_26_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_26_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_27",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_27",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_27_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_27_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_27_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_28",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_28",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_28_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_28_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_28_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_29",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_30",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_30",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_30_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_30_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_30_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_31",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_32",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_32",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_32_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_32_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_32_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_33",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_33",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_33_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_33_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_33_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_34",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_34",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_34_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_34_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_34_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_35",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_35",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_35_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_35_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_35_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_36",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_36",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_36_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_36_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_36_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_37",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_37",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_37_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_37_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_37_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_38",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_39",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_39",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_39_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_39_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_39_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_40",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_40",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_40_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_40_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_40_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_41",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_41",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_41_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_41_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_41_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_42",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_42",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_42_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_42_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_42_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_43",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_43",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_43_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_43_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_43_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_44",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_44",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_44_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_44_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_44_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_45",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_45",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_45_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_45_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_45_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_46",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_46",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_46_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_46_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_46_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_47",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_47",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_47_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_47_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_47_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_48",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_48",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_48_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_48_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_48_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_49",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_49",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_49_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_49_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_49_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_50",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_50",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_50_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_50_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_50_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_51",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_51",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_51_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_51_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_51_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_52",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_52",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_52_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_52_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_52_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_53",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_53",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_53_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_53_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_53_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_54",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_55",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_55",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_55_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_55_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_55_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_56",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_56",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_56_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_56_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_56_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_57",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_57",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_57_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_57_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_57_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_58",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_58",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_58_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_58_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_58_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_59",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_59",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_59_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_59_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_59_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_60",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_60",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_60_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_60_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_60_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_61",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_62",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_62",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_62_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_62_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_62_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_63",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_63",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_63_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_63_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_63_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_64",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_64",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_64_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_64_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_64_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_65",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_65",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_65_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_65_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_65_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_66",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_66",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_66_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_66_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_66_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_67",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_68",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_69",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_70",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_70",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_70_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_70_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_70_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_71",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_71",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_71_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_71_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_71_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_72",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_72",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_72_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_72_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_72_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_73",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_73",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_73_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_73_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_73_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_74",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_74",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_74_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_74_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_74_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_75",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_76",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_76",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_76_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_76_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_76_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_77",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_77",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_77_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_77_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_77_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_78",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_78",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_78_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_78_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_78_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_79",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_79",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_79_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_79_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_79_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_80",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_80",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_80_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_80_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_80_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_81",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_81",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_81_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_81_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_81_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_82",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_82",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_82_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_82_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_82_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_83",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_83",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_83_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_83_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_83_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_84",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_84",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_84_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_84_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_84_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_85",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_85",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_85_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_85_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_85_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_86",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_86",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_86_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_86_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_86_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_87",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_87",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_87_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_87_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_87_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_88",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_88",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_88_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_88_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_88_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_89",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_89",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_89_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_89_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_89_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_90",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_90",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_90_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_90_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_90_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_91",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_91",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_91_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_91_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_91_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_92",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_92",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_92_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_92_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_92_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_93",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_93",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_93_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_93_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_93_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_94",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_94",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_94_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_94_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_94_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_95",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_95",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_95_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_95_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_95_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_96",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_96",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_96_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_96_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_96_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_97",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_97",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_97_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_97_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_97_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_98",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_98",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_98_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_98_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_98_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_99",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_99",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_99_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_99_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_99_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_100",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_101",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_101",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_101_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_101_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_101_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_102",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_102",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_102_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_102_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_102_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_103",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_103",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_103_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_103_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_103_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_104",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_104",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_104_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_104_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_104_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_105",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_105",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_105_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_105_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_105_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_106",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_106",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_106_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_106_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_106_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_107",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_107",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_107_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_107_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_107_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_108",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_108",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_108_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_108_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_108_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_109",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_109",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_109_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_109_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_109_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_110",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_111",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_112",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_112",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_112_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_112_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_112_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_113",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_113",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_113_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_113_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_113_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_114",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_114",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_114_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_114_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_114_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_115",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_116",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_116",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_116_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_116_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_116_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_117",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_117",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_117_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_117_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_117_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_118",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_118",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_118_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_118_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_118_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_119",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_119",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_119_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_119_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_119_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_120",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_120",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_120_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_120_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_120_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_121",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_121",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_121_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_121_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_121_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_122",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_122",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_122_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_122_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_122_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_123",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_124",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_124",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_124_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_124_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_124_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_125",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_125",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_125_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_125_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_125_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_126",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_127",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_127",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_127_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_127_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_127_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_128",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_128",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_128_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_128_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_128_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_129",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_129",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_129_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_129_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_129_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_130",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_130",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_130_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_130_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_130_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_131",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_131",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_131_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_131_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_131_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_132",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_132",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_132_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_132_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_132_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_133",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_134",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_134",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_134_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_134_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_134_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_135",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_135",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_135_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_135_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_135_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_136",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_136",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_136_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_136_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_136_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_137",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_138",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_138",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_138_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_138_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_138_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_139",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_140",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_140",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_140_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_140_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_140_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_141",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_141",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_141_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_141_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_141_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_142",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_143",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_143",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_143_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_143_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_143_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_144",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_144",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_144_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_144_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_144_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_145",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_145",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_145_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_145_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_145_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_146",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_146",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_146_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_146_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_146_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_147",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_147",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_147_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_147_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_147_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_148",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_148",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_148_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_148_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_148_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_149",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_149",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_149_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_149_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_149_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_150",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_150",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_150_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_150_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_150_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_151",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_151",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_151_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_151_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_151_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_152",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_152",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_152_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_152_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_152_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_153",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_153",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_153_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_153_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_153_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_154",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_154",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_154_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_154_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_154_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_155",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_155",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_155_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_155_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_155_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_156",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_156",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_156_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_156_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_156_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_157",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_157",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_157_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_157_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_157_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_158",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_158",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_158_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_158_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_158_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_159",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_159",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_159_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_159_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_159_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_160",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_160",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_160_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_160_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_160_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_161",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_161",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_161_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_161_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_161_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_162",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_162",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_162_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_162_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_162_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_163",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_163",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_163_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_163_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_163_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_164",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_164",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_164_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_164_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_164_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_165",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_165",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_165_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_165_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_165_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_166",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_166",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_166_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_166_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_166_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_167",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_167",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_167_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_167_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_167_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_168",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_168",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_168_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_168_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_168_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_169",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_169",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_169_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_169_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_169_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_170",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_170",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_170_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_170_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_170_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_171",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_172",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_172",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_172_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_172_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_172_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_173",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_173",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_173_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_173_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_173_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_174",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_174",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_174_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_174_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_174_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_175",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_175",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_175_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_175_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_175_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_176",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_176",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_176_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_176_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_176_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_177",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_177",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_177_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_177_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_177_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_178",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_178",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_178_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_178_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_178_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_179",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_179",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_179_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_179_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_179_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_180",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_180",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_180_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_180_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_180_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_181",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_182",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_182",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_182_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_182_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_182_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_183",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_183",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_183_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_183_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_183_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_184",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_184",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_184_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_184_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_184_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_185",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_185",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_185_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_185_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_185_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_186",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_186",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_186_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_186_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_186_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_187",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_187",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_187_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_187_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_187_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_188",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_188",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_188_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_188_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_188_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_189",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_189",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_189_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_189_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_189_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_190",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_191",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_191",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_191_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_191_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_191_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_192",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_192",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_192_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_192_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_192_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_193",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_193",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_193_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_193_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_193_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_194",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_194",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_194_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_194_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_194_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_195",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_195",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_195_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_195_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_195_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_196",
        "correctAnswer": "FALSE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "TRUE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_197",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_197",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_197_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_197_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_197_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_198",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_199",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_199",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_199_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_199_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_199_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_200",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_200",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_200_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_200_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_200_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_201",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_201",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_201_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_201_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_201_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_202",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_202",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_202_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_202_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_202_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_203",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_203",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_203_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_203_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_203_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_204",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_204",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_204_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_204_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_204_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_205",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_205",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_205_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_205_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_205_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_206",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_206",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_206_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_206_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_206_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_207",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_207",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_207_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_207_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_207_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_208",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_208",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_208_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_208_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_208_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_209",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_209",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_209_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_209_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_209_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_210",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_210",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_210_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_210_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_210_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_211",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_211",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_211_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_211_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_211_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_212",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_212",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_212_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_212_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_212_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_213",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_213",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_213_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_213_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_213_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_214",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_214",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_214_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_214_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_214_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_215",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_215",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_215_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_215_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_215_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_216",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_216",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_216_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_216_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_216_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 1,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_217",
        "correctAnswer": "TRUE",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "FALSE"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_218",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_218",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_218_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_218_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_218_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 0,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_219",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_219",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_219_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_219_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_219_3"
        ]
      },
      {
        "type": 0,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "PACK_5_QUESTION_220",
        "correctAnswer": "PACK_5_CORRECT_ANSWER_220",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_220_1",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_220_2",
          "PACK_5_INCORRECT_ANSWER_220_3"
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]